(Penny:)Hey, you guys want
to play a drinking game?
Oh, well now, well now,
we'll never win.
(Sheldon:)You always play
the drinking game.
Not the drinking game,
a drinking game.
(Leonard:)To be fair, good at both.
(Amy:)What's the game?
(Penny:)All right, it's called
Never Have I Ever.
(Penny:)The rules are simple.
(Penny:)Someone says something
they've never done,
(Penny:)but if you have done it,
you take a drink.
(Leonard:)I've never played that before.
(stammers)
Hey, now, wait.
(Sheldon:)Have we started?
Do I drink?
(Sheldon:)What is happening?
Okay.
(Penny:)Calm down.
I'll go first.
(Penny:)All right, let's see.
(Penny:)Never have I ever...
(Amy:)She's trying
to think of something
(Amy:)she's never done before.
(Amy:)This could take a while.
(Penny:)Very funny.
(Penny:)Okay, never have I ever...
(Penny:)Yeah, you know what?
(Penny:)Let's just circle back.
(Leonard:)Okay, I'll go.
(Leonard:)Never have I ever been arrested.
(Sheldon:)So I drink.
(Amy:)No, it's only
if you've done it.
(Penny:)Got it.